skybound.ca 2009-06-14

# Skybound's Home Page

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor  information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)
  *  To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)
  * To send periodic emails (Customers will not be subscribed to a mailing list unless explicit permission is given.)
  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without you consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their customer account (whose link is provided in the purchase confirmation email). 

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.skybound.ca. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on **September 10, 2008**. 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. Or, you can proceed to our contact form. 

www.skybound.ca  
2861 Merrittville Hwy.  
Fonthill, ON L0S 1E6  
Canada  
support (at) skybound.ca  
+1 877-4-SKYBOUND (+1 877-475-9268)
